so the last video was 96 wrong alright
so that makes this 197 Apple number 97
and I I didn't graduate 96 my sister
dick I graduate ID 8 which would be the
next one but it made me think about
graduation I'm school and how you think
about we should have like a non-union
app that was not the best idea and then
it writing something else and I didn't
oh just online school especially for
kids that are older and if the choice is
gene dropping out and doing amazing
online course other people I know they
exist in many different ways the the
they called MOOCs massive online school
community something I noticed and source
but and but being able to facilitate
corporations working together with other
students just pretty much home based
learning and homeschooling and making
sure kids are having fun learning at
every age I'm sure we can coordinate on
that one and as we don't
like with toffee in our public schools
maybe can't afford private school or cat
fun an adequate private school that we
can afford then we can help create
together a school system that works and
maybe that's helping home school but
coordinating with everybody else so that
you're the math teacher someone else's a
science teacher someone else teaches
what workshop and making sure that your
kid has if they can create their own
course schedule I mean sorry they're
what they want to learn and then figure
out a way to learn that so every kid
could have that and so that is by remind
high school education each was both
amazing done horrible at all at the same
time as everyone knows I'm sure is Apple
number 97